30 Day Guarantee

Free Shipping Over $55 - Free Gift over $80

    * Back
        * Back
        * Back
        * Back
        * Back
        * Back
        * Back

    * Back

You haven't linked a page yet.

Privacy Policy
==============

**Effective date: January 1, 2020**

WE TAKE PRECAUTIONS WITH USER INFORMATION AND PERSONAL DATA. We value our users and respect your privacy.  
  
This Website is operated by Allstar Innovations (“we/our/us”). “You/your” means you as a user of the Website. “User” means all users of this Website. We offer this Website, including all information, tools and services available from this Website, to you conditioned upon your acceptance of all the terms, conditions, policies and notices stated here.  
  
WE TAKE PRECAUTIONS WITH USER INFORMATION AND PERSONAL DATA. We value our users and respect your privacy. We collect information about you through the Website in an effort to fulfill orders for products, improve your online experience and to communicate with you about our products, services and promotions. This Privacy Policy describes the personal information we collect about you, why we collect it, how we use it, and when we share it with third parties. This Privacy Policy also describes the choices you can make about how we collect and use certain of that information. The above excludes text messaging originator opt-in data and consent; this information will not be shared with any third parties.  
  
By accessing this Website, you acknowledge this Website Privacy Policy and agree to be bound by the terms hereof and the Terms of Use set forth on the Website. If there is anything you do not understand please write any inquiry to Allstar Products Group, PO Box 241, Hawthorne NY 10532. If at any time you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this Website.  
  
We reserve the right to change or update this Privacy Policy by posting such changes or updates to the Website. Amendments to this Privacy Policy will be posted at this URL and will be effective when posted. It is your responsibility to review any such changes or updates and check the Website from time to time to be sure you understand all terms and conditions, agreements and policies of the Website and are in compliance with them. You can tell if the policy has changed by checking the last modified date that appears at the end of this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Website following the posting of any amendment, modification or change shall constitute your acceptance thereof.  
  
**OVERVIEW**  
Information about our data collection during the prior 12 months is described below.  
  
You can access, delete and control certain uses of your information as set forth in the “**Opt-Out” and “Rights to Your Information**” sections below.  
  
**Categories of Personal Information**:

* Contact information and other information about you such as your name, telephone number, email address and physical address and demographic information.
* Financial information, product information, including credit card information.
* Online identifiers such as username, cookies, hashed email addresses, mobile device IDs including advertising identifiers, IP address, type of browser, operating system, date and time information and other technical information about your computer and browsing information.

**Sources of such Personal Information:**

* Collected from you directly through the Website or from your communications with us.
* Collected from you directly when you purchase our products through the Website.
* Collected by us when you visit our Website or interact with online advertisements, and from our partners who collect the information from you directly when you visit our partners’ sites or use our partners’ search engines.

**Business Purpose for such Personal Information:**

* We use such information to provide you our products and services, process and communicate with you about your orders, respond to inquiries we receive from you, send you marketing communications and as otherwise described in “**Use of Your Personal Information**” below.
* We use such information to provide you our products and services, and process your orders.
* We use such information to improve our Website and services, to deliver targeted advertising about goods and services that may be of interest to you, to assist anti-fraud services and as otherwise described in “**Use of Your Personal Information**” below.

**Categories of Third Parties with whom information is shared:**

* We share such information with our service providers and as otherwise described in “**Sharing Personal Information With Third Parties**” below.
* We share such information with our service providers to process your order.
* We share such information with our service providers, affiliates and advertising partners, sell this information to our customers and as otherwise described in “**Sharing Personal Information With Third Parties**” below.
* As used in this Privacy Policy, “personal information” is information that directly or indirectly identifies a specific person, such as name, telephone number, physical address, or email address.  
      
    **1\. Information We Collect From You**  
    We will ask you for certain kinds of personal information (“Personal Information”) to provide the services you request. This information includes:  
      
    Ordering – When you place an order we ask for your name, address, phone number and email address. You may be required to provide credit card details. We will never share your credit card details with any other party except to process your order. By placing an order with us your information may be stored with us.  
      
    Email List - When you place an order, you will be added to our email list. You will have the option to be removed from our email list by clicking the “unsubscribe” button found at the bottom of the emails we send you.  
      
    Calls to Customer Service/Participation in Promotions/Sweepstakes or Surveys- If you call our Customer Service center or participate in one of our promotions or sweepstakes or user surveys, we may ask for additional information, such as your age, interests or product preferences.  
      
    **2\. Information We Collect Automatically or From Others**  
      
    2.1 Through your use of this Website, we may also collect certain information from you that does not directly identify you as an individual. It is measured anonymously and only in the aggregate.  
      
    2.2 The Website may use cookies. A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a website that is saved on your hard drive by your computer’s browser. Cookies help us remember you when you return to the Website. Cookies also hold information to personalize and enhance your experience and to gather website statistical data, such as which pages are visited, the Internet provider’s domain name and the addresses of the sites you visited immediately before coming to and immediately after leaving the Website. The information in the cookies lets us trace your “clickstream” activity (i.e., the paths taken by users of the Website as they move from page to page) to enable us to better serve our users by revealing which portions of the Website are the most popular. You may disable cookies on your browser. Please see the “**Opt-Out**” section below for more information on how to do so.  
      
    2.3 We may also use “pixel tags” (sometimes called “web beacons” or “clear gifs”), which are tiny graphic images, on the Website. Pixel tags help us analyze Users’ online behavior and measure the effectiveness of the Website and our advertising and marketing. We may also use other analytical tools to evaluate site performance through the use of aggregated data, which does not directly identify you. We work with service providers that help us track, collect, and analyze this information.  
      
    2.4 Cookies, pixel tags, and/or other analytical tools that we may use on the Website may collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the features you use, the links you click, and other actions you take in connection with the Website. This information may include your computer’s Internet protocol (IP) address, your browser type, your operating system, date and time information, and other technical information about your computer. We may also track certain information about the identity of the website you visited immediately before coming to the Website. We do not otherwise track any information about your use of other websites.  
      
    2.5 Cookies, pixel tags, and/or other analytical tools in our emails may be used to track your interactions with those messages, such as when you receive, open, or click a link in an email message from us. The www.blackwolfnation.com uses cookies to help keep track of items you put into your shopping cart including when you have abandoned your cart and this information is used to determine when to send cart reminder messages via SMS.  
      
    2.6 We may also work with businesses that use tracking technologies to deliver advertisements on our behalf across the Internet. These companies may collect information about your visits to the Website and your interaction with our advertising and other communications.  
      
    2.7 We may combine the information collected through cookies, pixel tags and other analytical tools with other information we may have collected from you. This information may be used to improve our Website, to personalize your online experience, to help us deliver information to you, to determine the effectiveness of advertising, and for other internal business purposes.  
      
    2.8 We do not track users over time and across third party websites to provide targeted advertising and therefore do not respond to Do Not Track signals.  
      
    **3\. Use of Your Personal Information**  
    We use the Personal Information we collect for various purposes, including:  
      
    to complete your purchase transactions  
      
    to provide the services you request  
      
    to keep you informed about the status of your orders  
      
    to identify your product and service preferences, so we can notify you of new or additional products, services, and promotions that might be of interest to you  
      
    to notify you of product recalls or provide other information concerning products you have purchased  
      
    to improve our merchandise selections, customer service, and overall Website experience  
      
    to communicate with you by email, postal mail, telephone, text message, or other means  
      
    **4\. Sharing Personal Information With Third Parties**  
    4.1 We may share, sell or trade your Personal Information gathered online with third parties. We may contribute to or participate in cooperative databases, which give other companies access to such Personal Information.  
      
    4.2 We may disclose your Personal Information when legally required to do so, to cooperate with law enforcement investigations or other legal proceedings, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Website, to limit our legal liability and protect our rights or to protect the rights, property or safety of Users of this Website or the public.  
      
    4.3 We may also disclose your Personal Information to outside individuals and/or companies that help us bring you the products and services we offer and to create, operate, and maintain our Website. For example, we may work with third parties to: (a) manage a database of customer information; (b) assist us in distributing e-mails; (c) assist us with direct marketing and data collection; (d) provide data storage and analysis; (e) provide fraud prevention; (f) provide customer service; (g) provide product fulfillment and shipping services; and (h) provide other services designed to assist us in developing and running our Website and maximizing our business potential. We require that these outside companies agree to keep all information shared with them confidential and to use the information only to perform their obligations to us.  
      
    4.4 In addition, if we go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred.  
      
    4.5 Our Website may allow users to post comments and other content to our Website. Any Personal Information that you post to our Website will become public information and will be accessible by other users of the Website. In addition and if applicable, your user name will be viewable by other users, and we therefore encourage you to use a user name that is not your actual name. We have no responsibility to maintain the privacy or security of any such Personal Information that you may choose to post to our Website.  

    **5\. Sales of Information**  
    We may sell your Personal Information to third parties, subject to your right to opt-out of those sales (See the “**Opt-Out**” and “**Rights to Your Information**” sections below).   
      
    In the preceding twelve (12) months, we have sold the categories of Personal Information in the chart set forth above.  
      
    **6\. Your Security**  
    6.1 We strive to keep your Personal Information private and safe. We take commercially reasonable physical, electronic and administrative steps to maintain the security of Personal Information collected, including limiting the number of people who have physical access to database servers, as well as employing electronic security systems and password protections that guard against unauthorized access. In addition, it is our policy to never send your credit card number via e-mail. Please note that e-mail is not encrypted and is not considered to be a secure means of transmitting credit card information, so please do not send us your credit card number by email.  
      
    6.2 We use Secure Socket Layers (SSL), the industry standard in transferring information to process your orders. SSL encrypts, or translates, your order information into a highly indecipherable code, which is processed immediately. All credit card transactions occur in a secure area of the Website to protect you from any loss, misuse or alteration of information collected. When you have finished shopping and begin the checkout process, you will move into the secure area of the Website. Once you have entered, the page address (URL) will change from “http” to “https” to let you know you are in a secure area. Also, a key or a closed lock will appear in the lower right hand corner of your screen to notify you of this change. You will remain in this secure zone for the entire checkout process.  
      
    6.3 Unfortunately, despite our best efforts, the transmission of data over the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure. While we will use every reasonable means to ensure the security of information you transmit through the Website, we cannot guarantee that such information will not be intercepted by third parties. We will, however, prosecute any unauthorized or fraudulent transactions to the fullest extent permitted by law.  
      
    **7\. Links to Other Websites**  
    7.1 While visiting the Website, you may link to websites operated by third parties or you may have come to the Website using a link found in another website. This does not mean that we endorse these websites or the goods or services they provide. We do not make any representations or warranties about any website that may be linked to the Website. Such other websites are independent from us, and we have no control over, or responsibility for, their information, products or activities.  
      
    7.2 In addition, our privacy practices may differ from those of these other websites. If you provide Personal Information at one of those websites, you are subject to the privacy policy of the operator of that website, not our Privacy Policy. Please make sure you understand the other website’s privacy policy before providing Personal Information.  
      
    **8\. Social Networking Services**   
    The Website may integrate with social networking services. We do not control such services and are not liable for the manner in which they operate. While we may provide you with the ability to use such services in connection with our Website, we are doing so merely as an accommodation and, like you, are relying upon those third party services to operate properly and fairly.  
      
    You should be aware that Personal Information which you voluntarily include and transmit online in a publicly accessible blog, social network or otherwise online may be viewed and used by others. We are unable to control such uses of your Personal Information, and by using such services you assume the risk that the Personal Information provided by you may be viewed and used by third parties.  
      
    **9\. Opt-Out**  
    You will receive promotional emails from us only if you have asked to receive them. If you do not want to receive e-mails from us you may click on the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any email communication sent by us. Please allow us 10 business days from when the request was received to complete the removal, as some of our promotions may already have been in process before you submitted your request.  
      
    If you want to stop or restrict the placement of cookies or flush any cookies that may already be on your computer or device, please refer to and adjust your web browser preferences. Further information on cookies is available at www.allaboutcookies.org. By deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies you may not be able to access certain areas or features of our Website or some of its functionality may be affected. Cookies and similar items are not used by us to automatically retrieve information that can identify you from your device without your knowledge.   
      
    **10\. Rights to Your Information**  
    If you reside in California or in a jurisdiction that provides similar rights, under CCPA or applicable law, you have specific rights regarding your Personal Information. This section describes the rights that you have under CCPA, or other state laws as applicable, and explains how to exercise those rights.  
      
    • Right to Know About Personal Information Collected, Disclosed or Sold. You have the right to request that we disclose certain information to you about our collection, use, disclosure or sale of your Personal Information over the past 12 months. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request (see “**Exercising Access, and Deletion Rights**” below), and subject to certain limitations that we describe below, we will disclose such information to you. You have the right to request any or all of the following:
* The categories of Personal Information we collected about you.
* The categories of sources from which the Personal Information is collected.
* Our business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling that Personal Information.
* The categories of third parties with whom we share that Personal Information.
* The specific pieces of Personal Information we collected about you
*   
    Right to Request Deletion. You have the right to request that we delete any of your Personal Information that we collected from you and retained, subject to certain exceptions. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request (see “**Exercising Access, and Deletion Rights**” below), we will delete (and direct our service providers to delete) your Personal Information from our records. However, we may retain Personal Information that has been de-identified or aggregated. Furthermore, we may deny your deletion request if retaining the information is necessary for us or our service provider(s) in order to perform certain actions set forth under CCPA, such as detecting security incidents and protecting against fraud or illegal activity.   
      
    • Exercising Access and Deletion Rights. To exercise the access and deletion rights described above, please submit a request to us by:  
      
    Emailing us at privacy@allstarmg.com  
      
    Only you, or a person or business entity registered with the California Secretary of State that you authorize to act on your behalf (an “authorized agent”), may make the requests set forth above. You may also make a request on behalf of your minor child.   
      
    The request should include your contact information and describe your request with sufficient detail that allows us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it. In addition, you should provide sufficient information (including your full name, address, product purchased, order number) that allows us to reasonably verify that you are the person about whom we collected the personal information or an authorized representative.  
      
    We will respond to consumer requests in a reasonably timely manner. If we require extra time to respond, we will inform you of the reason and extension period in writing.  
      
    In order to protect the security of your Personal Information, we will not honor a request if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm the Personal Information relates to you. The method used to verify your identity will vary depending on the nature of the request. Generally speaking, verification will be performed by matching the identifying information provided by you to the Personal Information that we already have.  
      
    Any disclosures we provide will only cover the 12-month period preceding our receipt of your request. We are not obligated to provide the information set forth above under “Right to Know About Personal Information Collected, Disclosed or Sold” more than twice in a 12-month period.  
      
    We do not charge a fee to process or respond to your verifiable consumer request unless it is excessive, repetitive, or manifestly unfounded. If we determine that the request warrants a fee, we will tell you why we made that decision and provide you with a cost estimate before completing your request.   
      
    • Personal Information Sales Opt-Out and Opt-In Rights. You have the right to direct us to not sell your personal information at any time (the "right to opt-out"). We do not sell the personal information of consumers we actually know are less than 16 years of age, unless we receive affirmative authorization (the "right to opt-in") from either the consumer who is at least 13 and less than 16 years of age, or the parent or guardian of a consumer less than 13 years of age.  
      
    To exercise the right to opt-out, you (or your authorized representative) may submit a request to us by visiting the following Internet Web page: [Do Not Sell My Personal Information](https://boballstar.wufoo.com/forms/do-not-sell-my-personal-information/)  
      
    Alternatively, you may submit an opt-out request by emailing us at privacy@allstarmg.com.   
      
    • Non-Discrimination. We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your CCPA rights, including, but not limited to, by:
* Denying you goods or services.
* Charging you different prices or rates for goods or services, including through granting discounts or other benefits, or imposing penalties.
* Providing you a different level or quality of goods or services.
* Suggesting that you may receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.

8.   
    **“Spoofing” And “Phishing”**  
    A common Internet scam is known as “spoofing” or “phishing.” This occurs when you receive an email from what appears to be a legitimate source requesting Personal Information from you. Please be aware that we will not send you any emails requesting you to verify credit card, bank information, or any other Personal Information. If you ever receive an email that appears to be from us requesting such information from you, DO NOT respond to it, and DO NOT click on any links appearing in the email.  
      
    **9\. Children and Privacy**  
    The Website is not meant for children, and we will not knowingly collect any Personal Information from children under the age of 13 without verified parental consent. We will remove from our files any Personal Information of anyone we discover to be under 13 years old. Our online contests or sweepstakes are restricted to entrants who are at least 18 years old. We are concerned about the safety of children when they use the Internet, and we understand that children may not understand all the provisions of our Privacy Policy or make informed decisions about the choices that are made available to adult users of the Website.  
      
    **10\. Your California Privacy Rights**  
    Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of Personal Information we share with third parties or corporate affiliates for those third parties or corporate affiliates’ direct marketing purposes. That notice will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with which it was shared, along with their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: Allstar Products Group, PO Box 241, Hawthorne NY 10532. Please allow 30 days for a response.  
      
    **11\. Disclosure for Legal Purposes**  
    You hereby authorize us to disclose any of your Personal Information pursuant to judicial and administrative proceedings and to law enforcement or government agencies if we believe the disclosure is necessary or appropriate. You also authorize us to disclose Personal Information if we believe the disclosure is necessary or appropriate in the event of an investigation of improper or illegal conduct in connection with the Website, such as fraud, misrepresentation, intellectual property infringement, or other activity that may put us at risk for liability.  
      
    **12\. Non-Confidential Information**  
    We do not want you to send to us any confidential or proprietary information through email or otherwise. Any information, materials, suggestions, ideas or comments sent to us will be considered non-confidential, and by submitting the same to us, you are giving us the absolute right to use, modify, reproduce, transmit, display and distribute the information for any purpose whatsoever, with no payment or other compensation to you. However, we will not use your name unless we are required by law to identify the source of the materials, information, suggestions, ideas or comments, or unless we first obtain your permission.  
      
    **13\. Assignment**  
    We may freely assign this Privacy Policy or any of our rights and/or obligations hereunder.  
      
    **14\. Contact**  
    If you have any questions about your privacy or security at the Website, please write to Allstar Products Group, PO Box 241, Hawthorne NY 10532 and include your name, address and email address in the message. If you do not receive a response from us within 30 days, please send us another letter as your original correspondence may not have been received.

* If you elect to receive marketing text messages from us, either via our website or by sending a text message indicating your consent, you are providing your prior express written consent to receive recurring marketing or promotional Text text messages from us (each, a “Text Message”) sent through an automatic telephone dialing system. These may include cart abandon messages. Message frequency varies. This service is optional and is not a condition for purchase. You can opt out of receiving any further Text Messages from us at any time by replying “STOP” to any Text Message you receive from us. For help, reply “HELP” to any Text Message you receive from us or email textsupport@wunderkind.co.In addition to any fee of which you are notified, your mobile provider’s message and data rates may apply to our confirmation Text Message and all subsequent Text Message correspondence according to your individual rate plan provided by your wireless carrier. Please consult your mobile service carrier’s pricing plan to determine the charges for browsing data and sending and receiving Text Messages. Under no circumstances will we or our affiliates be responsible for any Text messaging or wireless charges incurred by you or by a person that has access to your wireless device or telephone number. If your carrier does not permit Text messages, you may not receive the Text Messages.Neither we nor the wireless carriers (such as T-Mobile) will be liable for any delays in the receipt of, or failure to deliver, any Text Messages, as delivery is subject to effective transmission from your network operator. Text Message services are provided on an “AS IS” basis. Data obtained from you in connection with any Text Message services may include your cell phone number, your provider’s name and the date, time and content of your text messages. We may use this information in accordance with our Privacy Policy to contact you and to provide the services you request from us. For more information on how we use telephone numbers, please read our Privacy Policy.If you change or deactivate the phone number you provided, you have an affirmative obligation to update your account information and the phone number(s) attached to your account to prevent us from inadvertently communicating with anyone who acquires any phone number(s) previously attributed to you, and any new phone number(s) you attach to your account may receive our standard marketing Text Messages unless you also unsubscribe via the above procedures. 
* _We may securely transfer information you share on our site with third party partners for the_ _purposes of marketing and advertising attribution and measurement. These partners may_ _place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer or device and may securely share_ _data between our servers and theirs_

### Fast Shipping

Orders ship within 1-2 days

### Contact Us

EARLY ACCESS TO SHOP BLACK FRIDAY DEALS
---------------------------------------

Get on the list to shop Black Friday before everyone!

### Black Wolf Deals + Kits

### Black Wolf Hair Care

### Black Wolf Face + Body

### Black Wolf Ear Care

Quick links

Newsletter

Be the first to receive updates on new arrivals, special promos and sales.

   Email address 

This site is protected by hCaptcha and the hCaptcha [Privacy Policy](https://hcaptcha.com/privacy) and [Terms of Service](https://hcaptcha.com/terms) apply.

Search here... 

Cancel

Popular products

[

Haircare Bundle

10

$32.00](https://blackwolfnation.com/products/haircare-bundle)

29% Off

[

Sonic Scrubber Exfoliation System

$71.00$49.99](https://blackwolfnation.com/products/sonic-scrubber-body-wash-face-wash)

FSA/HSA ELIGIBLE

[

WUSH™ PRO Ear Cleaner

1477

Color

$59.00

Color](https://blackwolfnation.com/products/wush)

{"themeColor":"#574cd5","iconColor":"#574cd5","showLogo":true,"topBottomPosition":100,"rightLeftPosition":10,"iconSize":"extra-small","iconCustomSize":64,"position":"middle-right"}
